

ERNEST AKUBUEZE

PYTHON/BACKEND **ENGINEER**

Skills

Python

Flask

MongoDB & Postgres

REST API

HTML5 & CSS

Contact



+2348165970350



delernestoa@gmail.com



kingdel.herokuapp.com



Ernest (Del) Akubueze

Profile

Experienced python developer and backend engineer. Knowledgeable in data handling, backend & frontend development, testing and deployment. Equipped with Python, Rest APIs, Flask, MongoDB, Postgres, PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS, JS, webscraping and other promising skills. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. Exploring Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence.

Work Experience



Python Developer, Qubators

JANUARY 2022 - Present

Collaborated and managed other team members to create innovating brand ideas and project initiatives.

- Achieved "Soundcode App"
- Achieved Full Stack Web Devs using Python Flask, Html & CSS, MySQL,
- Achieved Cloud Hosting and Database management using MongoDB and Postgres.



Python Developer, Free Lancer

MAY 2020 - JANUARY 2022

- Completed over 25 freelance jobs and contributed to various freelance communities.
- Effectively added to diifferent Github repos.
- Participated and Won in 2020 Hacktober Fest
- Acquired more knowledge and skills in Back End Engineering

Education



Bachelor of Engineering

2017 - | University of Nigeria, Nsukka

• Currently undergoing an Electrical Engineering Program

Diploma in Electrical/Electronics Engineering

2016 - 2017 | University of Lagos, Akoka

• Graduated with Distinction

West African Senior Secondary Examination Certificate

2009 - 2016 | Bill Gates Skills College

• Graduated with High Honors

Reference



Emmanuel Sunday from Qubators

nuel.mailbox@gmail.com | +2348065855469